https://vanderbiltcu.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Home » Privacy Policy
Download Printable Version Here
FACTS
What Does Vanderbilt University Credit Union Do with your Personal Information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
account transactions and checking account information
employment information and payment history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons Vanderbilt University Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Vanderbilt University Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes-
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes-
to offer our products and services to you
NO
We don't share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
YES
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Vanderbilt University Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes-
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes-
to offer our products and services to you
NO
We don't share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
YES
For our everyday business purposes-
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
Questions?
call (615) 936-0300 or go to www.vanderbiltcu.org
What we do
How does Vanderbilt University Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards adn secured files and buildings.
How does Vanderbilt University Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
apply for a loan or give us your employment information
provide account information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Vanderbilt University Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, plastic card processors (credit/debit/ATM), financial statement publishers or printers, consumer reporting agencies, data processors, and check/share draft printers.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group's MEMBERCONNECT
